The air feels wrong.
Yin energy, death energy...
and a trace of something alive stirring.
Who cares what energy it is!
Zhang Tianyou!
Get over here and draw out the poison first!
You got this poison from years of handling corpses,
with the poison seeping into your body through the skin.
This Corpse Poison of yours is quite severe.
You must have started raiding tombs as a kid.
We aren't as professional as The Four Great Families.
We have to risk our lives
just to get some underworld riches.
Zhang Tianyou,
don't forget what you promised me.
You'll carve out a large piece of Sheng family territory for me.
Don't worry.
I won't go back on my word.
You're quite bold.
No wonder my men said you were something else.
What did your men tell you?
I know your background is far from ordinary.
And becoming the Chief isn't your ultimate goal.
But do you know that
even if you gather all the Talismans and Seal Eyes,
you still won't find the Tidal Tomb you're looking for?
Because
your Dragon-Seeking Ruler alone isn't enough.
You have to find the descendants of
the Dragon-Seeking Zhang Family tied to that tomb.
But they died out a long time ago.
Something's wrong.
What's wrong?
Do you remember when we first came in?
This statue's feet were pointing straight at the coffin.
Are they alive?
They don't look like living things.
They're more like puppets driven by some force.
They turned around!
I get it now.
This isn't where the Qi family hides their talisman books.
These are the Mei family's seal-guarding puppets!
The Mei family's Celestial Seal must be hidden here.
Get ready to open the coffin.
Three, two, one. Open the coffin!
Let's go.
Tianting,
That outsider still can't be trusted.
I still need my son to step in personally.
Father.
Killing that brat
is as easy as squashing an ant.
I'm counting on you for tonight, my son.
Understood, Father.
Just wait and see.
Zhang Tianyou!
You punk,
you made me lose face in front of Ling Yu.
Tonight,
I'm going to show you
how ruthless I can be.
Did I get fat,
or did the wall get higher?
Young Master, that idiot has started.
It's fine. Our walls are high.
Let him have his fun.
I refuse to believe this!
Young Master, that idiot is still trying.
No rush.
Let him get some exercise.
Young Master!
He's almost up here.
So fast?
Thank heavens, I finally made it up.
Zhang Tianyou, your time is finally up.
You're finally here.
My leg!
My leg hurts!
My leg is broken!
My leg's broken!
I know.
Call a doctor!
My leg!
Easy, easy, easy.
My leg hurts!
VIP seating.
For me?
Thanks.
No problem.
Steady now.
My leg!
He comes as he pleases,
and leaves as he pleases.
The Sheng family's walls are still too easy to scale.
Have someone build the walls higher tomorrow.
And smear some tung oil on them.
Got it.
Tianyou,
over the past twenty years,
people in the Sheng clan have been dying suddenly.
Could it really be related to
what we provoked in the Tidal Tomb back then?
But right now,
there are only twelve days left
until that thing comes to claim our lives.
So I must gather the Talismans and Seal Eyes as soon as possible,
go to the Tidal Tomb, and destroy that thing.
Back then, The Four Great Families and the Dragon-Seeking Zhang Family teamed up for Geomancy,
but only the four families made it out.
Too many secrets from twenty years ago remain hidden.
It's a pity
I didn't even get the chance to ask your father
before he passed away.
Young Master!
How is Young Master Qi?
He's been sent back.
Did he say anything?
He was fairly calm.
Master Qi has a message for you.
He said...
I know.
Did he say
that everyone in the Sheng family better wash our necks,
because he's coming to behead us all tomorrow?
You're so smart, Young Master!
Where's my luggage?
I've packed everything for you.
Take care of yourself.
What are you guys doing?
Young Master
I brought the servants to pay respects to the Sheng Family Head.
Paying respects to the Family Head.
Family Head.
You can't just abandon us!
Are you still leaving?
I'll stay a bit longer.
My son's legs!
Master, please don't be too heartbroken.
Take care of your own health.
The Qi family is still counting on you.
If you collapse too,
how am I supposed to live?
Get out.
I want to be alone with Ting'er for a bit.
Let's go.
What is Dad going to do from now on?
Mother.
How is my dad?
Your dad?
He's having a deep emotional exchange with your older brother right now.
What an idiot.
What will our Qi family do now?
Dad!
Be gentle!
These are the keys to the Sheng family's thirteen warehouses.
Please check them.
Here are the account details for the Sheng family's
antique shops, pawnshops, and pharmacies.
Please look them over.
This is the territory distribution map
for the Sheng family among The Four Great Families.
Please review it.
Wan.
Mei.
Qi.
Where is the Sheng family?
Last year, the Qi and Sheng families redivided their territory.
What belongs to the Sheng family now
is right here.
According to the division,
the Sheng family can only practice Geomancy and explore here.
It's not even the size of a fingernail.
Hard to believe.
The Sheng family has been bullied quite badly all these years.
All right.
Since I'm taking over the Sheng family,
well,
we must take our territory back.
And win back our pride as well.
Good.
Doesn't the Qi family love to uphold justice?
Get the car ready.
No need to prepare any special outfits.
Just wrap up this Earth Vein Sutra for me.
As a thank-you gift.
Before I return,
sort out all these accounts for me.
Remember,
I didn't take over the Sheng family to listen to stories.
I'm here to rewrite them.
Yes, sir.
Is it really just you alone?
What did you expect?
They said following you is a death wish.
What idiot would willingly follow?
Don't worry.
I am the face of the Sheng family now.
That old fox Qi Lianhai,
even if he wants to drop all pretenses,
he still has to consider if there are other eyes watching.
Right?
Let's hope so.
If that still doesn't work,
I still have the Mei family's Celestial Seal.
Rats!
Ra-